export default [
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Sweden', 'USA', 'France', 'Italy'],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Italy', 'Sweden', 'USA', 'China'],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Spain', 'Canada', 'U.S.A.', 'Norway'],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Greece', 'Cyprus', 'Italy', 'Croatia'],
    correct: 3
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['India', 'Bali', 'Japan', 'Thailand'],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Denmark', 'Indonesia', 'Taiwan', 'China'],
    correct: 4
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Denmark', 'Vatican City State', 'Moldavia', 'China'],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Australia', 'Indonesia', 'Taiwan', 'China'],
    correct: 1
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['Denmark', 'Peru', 'Taiwan', 'China'],
    correct: 2
  },
  {
    question: 'What country does this look like?',
    answers: ['India', 'China', 'Egypt', 'Croatia'],
    correct: 3
  }
];
